

MARK ANTOHONY RODA

Web Developer/Software Developer



09276775451



rodamarkanthony90@gmail.com



Dama De Noche, Locatha, Looc, Lapu-Lapu City, Cebu 6015, Philippines



https://mark-anthony-roda.vercel.app

Language

C, C++, C#, PHP, JAVA, JavaScript

Framework/Libraries/UI Components

- NodeJS(Express, AdonisJS)
- ReactJS(NextJS)
- TailwindCss
- Bootstrap
- Mantine UI
- Ant Design

Database

- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- DynamoDB

Technical Skills

- Web development
- Mobile app development
- Backend and Frontend coding
- Database Designing
- System Analysis

Reference

Ryan Canseco

Senior Software Developer 09771662432 ryancanseco18@gmail.com

John Vincent Manuel

Software Development Manager 09079506811

Jv@halcyondigitalmedia.com

About Me

With 3 years in full-stack development, I specialize in AdonisJS for backend tasks, complemented by a sound understanding of frontend technologies, including Next.js. Proficient in tailwindCSS for styling and experienced in integrating UI components from Ant Design and Mantine, I bring a well-rounded skill set to full-stack development projects.

Experience

Software Developer Intern (WFH) Sep 2020 - Dec 2020 (Cerenimbus inc.,)

Worked virtually with web developers and assisted them in group web development projects. Resolved minor bug fixes.

Software Developer 2021 - Present (Halcyon Agyle)

Collaborated with a team of talented programmers, contributing to the development and enhancement of innovative software solutions.

Education

University of Cebu Lapu-Lapu and Mandaue

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2016 - 2020

Skills Summary

C#

NodeJs - AdonisJS	95%
ReactJS - NextJS	90%
JavaScript	90%
TailwindCSS	90%
NodeJs - Express	80%
PHP	80%
Mantine UI and Ant Design	80%
Bootstrap	80%
JAVA	70%
С	70%
C++	70%

70%